A Guide to the Tazewell family papers, 1623-1930
Library of Virginia
- 16 June 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  William Gaston in Raleigh NC to Littleton Waller Tazewell--draft and letter he'd sent to Tazewell must have been stolen--will send a duplicate right away--taken steps to figure out what happened
- 23 June 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  John Wickham to Littleton Waller Tazewell-Tazewell's daughter's health-crops-Tazewell elected to convention
- 28 June 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  William F. Wickham of Hanover County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-sending statement of debt from Bouldin as exr. of Ross-glad that convention will bring Tazewell to Richmond-can visit-invites Tazewell family to plantation
- 3 July 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Chr. [?] Fry to Waller and Foster concerning a debt owed him
- 14 July 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Waller and Foster of Boston to Christopher Fry of Norfolk-an account
- 20 July 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  William B. Giles to Littleton Waller Tazewell-received a letter from Lafayette regarding emancipating slaves in Virginia-Giles will reply-asks for a copy of Tazewell's report on Colonization made in the Senate a few years ago
- 25 July 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Edward Berry of York County to John N. Tazewell-business concerning Hodges-attempting a translation which might send to Tazewell-returning books-asks him to send some other volumes-John's legal prospects
- 25 July 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell of Norfolk-Jackson's visit interfering with Tazewell's departure-family and personal news
- 2 August 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  James M. Garnett [Essex?] to Littleton Waller Tazewell-school he's trying to open-possibly Tazewell's son might attend
- 3 August 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  summons by Superior Court of Chancery in suit of Cary Wilkinson vs. John Warburton late sheriff of James City County and exr. of William P. Harris, Littleton Waller Tazewell, exr of Benjamin Taliaferro, et al
- 6 August 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  order of the court in suit of Cary Wilkinson vs. John Warburton late sheriff of James City County and exr. of William P. Harris, Littleton Waller Tazewell, exr of Benjamin Taliaferro, et al
- 13 August 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell in Philadelphia to John N. Tazewell of Norfolk-purchased and transferred two shares of stock for bank of the United States to John-Louisa has written mother and will probably have given details of trip-will be in NY soon and then to Saratoga Springs-Sally hasn't coughed since leaving home
- 30 September 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Benjamin Watkins Leigh of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-encouraging Tazewell to be at opening session-discussion of who will be convention president
- 6 October 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby in Richmond to John N. Tazewell in Norfolk-convention news-Monroe president and a terrible one at that-anecdote about Madison and Tazewell-John Randolph-Philip Doddridge-James Wickham
- 20 October 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell in Richmond to John N. Tazewell of Norfolk-a note for Mrs. Decatur-get measurements for shoes from William Smith for the eastern shore people so that Tazewell can have them made in Richmond-send up his clothes from NY when can-nothing being done in the convention and Tazewell is sick of the place-doesn't like his hotel-if John's interested in seeing things should come up next week-has only heard from Littleton
- 20 October 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby in Richmond to John N. Tazewell in Norfolk-convention news-clash between Leigh and Johnson-Leigh defends old constitution from Johnson and Mercer-Johnson says inhibits education-Mercer offers guarantee that slaves won't be heavily taxed-Tazewell spoke against proposition of Judge Summers for 5000 people for apportionment of the house
- 30 October 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Hugh Lawson White of TN to Littleton Waller Tazewell in Richmond-letter of introduction for Mr. Grundy-he may watch some of the proceedings
- 31 October 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  receipt from John Widgen to Ann S. Tazewell for payment for painting done
- 31 October 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby to John N. Tazewell-Dick Morris of Hanover-Alexander Campbell, a poor speaker in Grigsby's eyes-Scott of Fauquier-next week the great men-Leigh, Johnson, Mercer-asks Tazewell to send Grigsby's copy of Randolph's speech on retrenchment
- 20 November 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Francis Baylies of Taunton MA to Littleton Waller Tazewell-complaining about collector of Boston, David Henshaw-damaging to Jackson's administration in Boston
- 21 November 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby to John N. Tazewell-needs counter-memorials to balance those calling for his resignation from the convention (now that he is a member)-couldn't answer question about General Taylor-debates in convention-dinner for James Barbour-didn't attend
- 21 November 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  John Cowper-note on renting Mrs. Nivison's house for the Marine Insurance Company-will only rent bottom floor this time-house needs some repairs
- 24 November 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby to John N. Tazewell-general convention news
- 28 November 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Receipt from Edward Barry to John N. Tazewell for payment of execution in suit of Prosser vs. Hodges--$52.41 after fees subtracted
- 8 December 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby to John N. Tazewell-general convention news-amusing anecdote-Tazewell spoke against popular election of governor
- 20 December 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  G. C. Verplanck of NY to Littleton Waller Tazewell-letter of introduction for Verplanck's brother
- 26 December 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby to John N. Tazewell-Convention news-several reform motions out-Tazewell might come out strong against them
- 29 December 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby to John N. Tazewell-Convention news
- 29 December 1829 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  William C. Whittle aboard the U.S. Ontario[?] to John N. Tazewell
- 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  draft of letters from Littleton Waller Tazewell to Miles King-concerning suit against the Navy for money King believes owed him-Tazewell agrees (may be incomplete)
- 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  copy of a letter, no names or dates, regarding the case of Miles King late Navy agent of Norfolk-possibly written by Tazewell who wrote the letters mentioned therein
- 9 January 1829 [1830] (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby to John N. Tazewell-convention news-Floyd elected governor by legislature
- 12 January 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Final settlement of the state accounts by the Board of Commissioners appointed for that purpose under the act "to provide more effectively for the settlements of accounts between the United States and the Individual States"
- 23 January 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby in Richmond to John N. Tazewell in Norfolk-has little news-John's father left some items in the hotel when he left which HBG now has in his possession and will forward to John-what little activity of the House of Delegates-the Norfolk Atheneum
- 25 January 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Commonwealth vs. Henry a slave belonging to A. Taylor-acquitted
- 3 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Cary Wilkinson vs. John Warburton former sheriff of James City County and committee of William P. Harris and with John Ambler exrs of William Wilkinson; and Littleton Waller Tazewell exr of Benjamin Taliaferro, and heir of Sophia A. Smith and in his own right, Charles H. Smith in his own right and as surviving exr of Larkin Smith and admr of estates of Ann M. Smith and Juliet M. Smith and William Smith; Alexander Henderson admr de bonis non of Sophia A. Smith, John H. Smith, Mary E. Brooke, and Mildred and Mary Henderson, all heirs of Ann M. Smith, Juliet Smith, and Larkin Smith, all deceased-court orders from the Circuit Superior Court of Williamsburg
- 3 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Cary Wilkinson vs. John Warburton former sheriff of James City County and committee of William P. Harris and with John Ambler exrs of William Wilkinson; and Littleton Waller Tazewell exr of Benjamin Taliaferro, and heir of Sophia A. Smith and in his own right, Charles H. Smith in his own right and as surviving exr of Larkin Smith and admr of estates of Ann M. Smith and Juliet M. Smith and William Smith; Alexander Henderson admr de bonis non of Sophia A. Smith, John H. Smith, Mary E. Brooke, and Mildred and Mary Henderson, all heirs of Ann M. Smith, Juliet Smith, and Larkin Smith, all deceased-court orders from the Circuit Superior Court of Williamsburg-printed copy with added note by commissioner's office dated 11 February 1830
- 3 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- 7 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  C. D. Whid[?] Cole, collector in Petersburg to William Francis of Norfolk-accounts of William Francis for goods imported into Norfolk
- 11 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Frederick Vincent of Norfolk to Littleton Waller Tazewell in Washington-regarding notice on Wilkinson vs. Warburton which had arrived in Norfolk
- 18 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  John G. Williamson of King and Queen County to John N. Tazewell of Norfolk-gives John directions to visit-game for hunting
- 18 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Samuel D. Ingham, Secretary of the Treasury to Littleton Waller Tazewell-regarding appointment of a collector at Norfolk
- 20 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  (and postscript added 21 February 1830)-Littleton Waller Tazewell to Andrew Jackson-regarding the case of Miles King for money King believes owed him
- 21 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell in Washington-politics-tariffs, internal improvements, western lands-affect the presidential election-present administration can't be as bad as previous for country or south-vote on constitution coming up-railroad from Petersburg to Roanoke (proposed)-other news
- 22 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Commonwealth vs. James a slave belonging to Mr. Hughes-acquitted
- 24 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to Andrew Jackson-regarding the case of Miles King for money King believes owed him
- 25 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell in Washington to John N. Tazewell of Norfolk-letters from John-asked commissioner Anderson to postpone taking accounts until he returns-release Cowper from rent, might rent to Lee-rent of wharf-wants memo of account with the BUS-account of Dr. Smith by William Smith-Wilson's application for taking census on Eastern Shore-warehouse on wharf-John's desire to hire Joshua Smith-send issues of the "Albion"-Loyall's case before House of Representatives
- 25 February 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  note from Littleton Waller Tazewell to Andrew Jackson-received the president's-case of Miles King
- 24 March 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell-regarding John's of the 19th-rent of wharf-sale of lot-legal matters-Mr. Foot's resolution
- April 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  testimony in [?]ings vs. Nixon
- April 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Dobyns vs. Thompson-suit settled-says see Mr. Thompson's letter of 19 July 1830
- 2 April 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to unknown recipient-why he hasn't responded to letter earlier
- 6 April 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-took daughter to Baltimore to have work done on a defect of spine-politics, internal improvements, past and present administrations
- 14 April 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  John Wickham to Littleton Waller Tazewell-regarding his previous letter (the above)-mentions trip to Baltimore-seeds Tazewell sent-received letter by General Wool
- 17 April 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Nathaniel Macon of NC to Littleton Waller Tazewell-thanks him for sending White's report on Indian affairs
- 22 April 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Arthur Emmerson J.P. of Norfolk County-affidavit of Thomas F. Nixon regarding a witness in a case for him
- 27 April 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell in Washington to John N. Tazewell-regarding proposition from Soulter
- 30 April 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell in Washington to John N. Tazewell-regarding health of Sarah Nivison
- May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Gaskins ad. Nixon-appeal warrant-cover
- May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Committee by Reilly ad. Patrick Corregan-peace warrant-cover
- 1 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-son went to Baltimore and picked up daughter-politics-may go to Baltimore-if does will try to stop in Washington
- 1 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby to John N. Tazewell-bidding farewell before leaving on his trip
- 7 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell-received John's letter of the 3rd-also saw copy of Norfolk Herald with news of mother-in-law's death-will be home as soon as possible
- 8 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  [?] Watson-drafts in the hands of Walter F. Jones in Norfolk
- 15 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Samuel Swarthout of NY to Littleton Waller Tazewell-thanks Tazewell for Tazewell's comments favorable to him in the Senate
- 18 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Hugh Lawson White to Littleton Waller Tazewell-vote on the library committee report-regrets Tazewell's absence and reason for it
- 22 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Hugh Lawson White to Littleton Waller Tazewell-Maysville Road Bill
- 24 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Thomas Kemp of Worcester England-power of attorney to Charles Hilditch and Thomas Hardy
- 24 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  will of Sarah Nivison written 19 February 1830-recorded 24 May 1830
- 24 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Diana Kemp, Matthew Wilkinson, and Benjamin Wilkinson of Worcester England-power of attorney to Charles Hilditch and Thomas Hardy
- 26 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to Samuel D. Ingham, Secretary of the Treasury-sending two certificates would like one in return for stock in the bank
- 26 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell of Norfolk to John Randolph of Charlotte County-recommending Mr. McLean of NY as secretary of legation to Russia for Randolph-if Randolph passes through Norfolk, expects him to visit-what Russia might be like when Randolph gets there
- 27 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to Severn E. Parker-concerning money owed Jacob G. Parker, dec'd by Judge Bouldin-Parker received this debt from Tazewell in payment for King's Creek property-now money is being collected-to be paid to S. E. Parker
- 27 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Hugh Lawson White to Littleton Waller Tazewell-Indian Bill passed the Senate-Jackson returned Maysville Road Bill with his objections to the House
- 28 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Hugh Lawson White to Littleton Waller Tazewell-whether they will meet again or not-White's losses
- 29 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Hugh Lawson White to Littleton Waller Tazewell-appointment of Mr. Noah-a convention with Denmark
- 31 May 1830 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Nicholas Biddle to Littleton Waller Tazewell-discussing the stocks of the BUS and how much they cost
- 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  account of Tazewell as executor for Benjamin Taliaferro [?]-incomplete
- 3 June 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-Tazewell's health-food and drink-tariff, commerce, agriculture-session of Congress-Randolph's appointment to Russia-president's popularity
- 20 June 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John Randolph-note inviting Randolph and any friends to Tazewell's house-anything else he can do
- 22 June 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  William S. Archer of Amelia County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-asks for Tazewell's pamphlet on the West Indies Trade-envies Tazewell's "black mark" for having a political opinion differing from the administration
- July 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  receipt for payment to the clerk of James City County Court for copy bill and answers in Taliaferro's ex against Wilkinson's exors.
- 9 July 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Rich[ard] [?] Peters [?] of Philadelphia to Littleton Waller Tazewell-Pennsylvania appointed commissioners to revise the statistics [?] of the state-some questions about how Virginia did it
- 14 July 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Hugh Blair Grigsby in New Haven[?] to John N. Tazewell of Norfolk-thanks for the letter-health is bad-upon return to Norfolk will travel up to the VA highlands with Tazewell-dismal professional prospects-studying only "hard" books-any romantic prospects for John among the ladies-regards to John's father-glad to hear he's well
- 16 July 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  inventory and appraisement of estate of Sarah Nivison of Norfolk-made by Littleton Waller Tazewell
- 19 July 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  William B. Selden of Norfolk to Littleton Waller Tazewell-son is leaving for France-asks Tazewell for letters of introduction to minister and other persons
- 22 July 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-thought about coming down to Norfolk and travelling over to the Eastern Shore with Tazewell-can't-glad to hear that Tazewell might visit during a trip to Essex County-his opinion-Tazewell's dislike of politics-travelling to the Virginia Springs
- 23 July 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  A. Pattison and A. Benton of Darlington, Britain, to Tilsey Graham of Norfolk regarding the late John Lawrence
- 24 July 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Edward Barry of York County to John N. Tazewell-legal matters in Elizabeth City County-left John's books at his (Barry's) father's in Norfolk
- August 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Commonwealth ads. Garrison and Forde
- 2 August 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to ?-Tazewell's purchase of King's Creek Plantation from estate of Dr. Parker
- 16 August 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  William Browne, judge of the Superior Courts of Chancery for the Districts of Williamsburg and Fredericksburg appointing John N. Tazewell a commissioner in chancery to act in the Williamsburg District
- 16 August 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  sales account of the estate of Sarah Nivison-sale of slaves
- 24 August 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  receipt from Humbleton Skipwith (signed by others for him) to Littleton Waller Tazewell for $131.37 1/2 for 1/4 part from sale of slaves from the estate of Sarah Nivison
- 25 August 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  receipt from Arthur Emmerson to Littleton Waller Tazewell for a male slave bequeathed to him by the will of Sarah Nivison-also received $60 for hire of the slave-received $16.50 from others
- 31 August 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  payment of rent from Dr. James Purcell to Thomas Balls
- 1 September 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- September 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  form for Thomas F. Nixon requesting a material witness in a suit against him by Mary Cowling-not filled in or signed
- 3 September 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell of Norfolk to John N. Tazewell in Philadelphia-John's health-rain in Norfolk, weather-if John goes to NY has some business he can conduct for him-family news
- 5 September 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell of Norfolk to John N. Tazewell in New York (delivered in Norfolk apparently)-John's health-Tazewell's schooner Elizabeth arriving in NY with Sweet Potatoes-asks John to check on them-money should be deposited in the branch of the bank of the U.S.-captain, John can use what they need-asks John to get him some Saratoga water-asks John to buy him some stocks-family news
- 9 September 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell-their previous correspondence-again asks John to purchase some stocks if possible-asks him to look for a school for Littleton Jr.-John's health-local news-French revolution of 1830-interesting comments concerning wars in Europe (sent to Philadelphia, forwarded to Norfolk)
- 15 September 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Summons-sheriff of Norfolk County to summon William Cary, Nancy Selmon and Ann Maria Robbin to appear in court to testify on behalf of Thomas F. Nixon in suit against him by Mary Cowling
- 16 September 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  statement of facts relating to an importation of dry goods made by William Francis in September 1828
- October 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell of Norfolk-their health-weather, drought-concern over food prices-opening of colonial trade by British-glad to hear Tazewell may visit
- 25 December 1830 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  Captain W. M. Crane of the U.S. Navy recommending Lt. Charles S. McCauley for command of a ship of war if a promotion opens
- 1830 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  receipts
- 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11 (Begin Misc. reel #675))
  account and receipt with clerk of the Circuit Superior Court of Law and Chancery for the county of James City-Isaac A. Coles, Humberton Skipwith and Helen and Sally (Sarah) Skipwith against Tazewell-for continuance
- 8 January 1830 [1831] (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell in Washington to John N. Tazewell of Norfolk-events in Washington have made getting time to write difficult-an impeachment-John's difficulty in transferring stock-hogs on the plantations-John's health-mentions the rift between Calhoun and Jackson
- 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  account with clerk of court of Williamsburg district-Isaac A. Coles, Humberton Skipwith and Helen and Sarah Skipwith against Tazewell-for continuance
- 5 January 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell in Washington-Tazewell's health-Wickham's travel to the springs and his health-legislature working on contested elections and reorganizing the courts-John Marshall-Virginia's political views
- 7 January 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Rudolph Bunner of Oswego County, NY to Littleton Waller Tazewell in Washington-discussing national politics-tariffs, banks, internal improvements-wide ranging
- 13 January 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  F[ortesque?] Whittle of Mecklenburg County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-legal problems with Macintosh over a trust deed Whittle made to Tazewell-properties in Norfolk, Mecklenburg, western part of the state
- 14 January 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-Leigh's right to a seat in the general assembly-whether Tazewell had spoken against Leigh-Leigh's right to it-Leigh and Tazewell-Tazewell and the Senate
- 1 February 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Humberton Skipwith of Albemarle County to Littleton Waller Tazewell-regarding an offer for property in Norfolk left by Sarah Nivison to Skipwith's daughter (her granddaughter)-regards to family
- 5 February 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell-John's health-the impeachment of Judge Peck by the House of Representatives-vote of the Senate
- 7 February 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  draft from John Patterson of Norfolk for $35 to be paid to J. J. Cohen and Brothers
- 13 February 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John N. Tazewell-sending letter by Mr. King-his health-John's health-not much in Congress-blackguardism rampant-attacks in Senate on postmaster, in house on Randolph-mentions a pamphlet will be coming out and will send it to John-letter of the 5th
- 13 February 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  John Wickham of Richmond to Littleton Waller Tazewell-death of his son Cary
- 18 February 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  Littleton Waller Tazewell to John Tazewell-brief note saying that he has sent the pamphlet mentioned above in two parts
- 22 February 1831 (Box 6, Folder 11)